<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2022-09-13T15:37:21.116Z"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="dylan_gibson@vfc.com"
        cq:lastReplicated="{Date}2022-09-13T15:37:42.860Z"
        cq:lastReplicatedBy="dylan_gibson@vfc.com"
        cq:lastReplicationAction="Activate"
        cq:lastRolledout="{Date}2022-09-13T15:37:21.125Z"
        cq:lastRolledoutBy="dylan_gibson@vfc.com"
        cq:template="/apps/vfcorp/templates/global/page-col-1"
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[cq:LiveRelationship,mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="Strava 15 - 15 - 15 Challenge"
        jcr:uuid="23ee565d-491b-4064-9701-87776ca5e728"
        sling:resourceType="vfcorp/components/global/page/page-col-1"
        sling:vanityPath="[/content/vfcorp/altra/north-america/en_us/terms/strava-15-15-15]"
        dataLayerErrorCode="400"
        frequency="always"
        noFollow="true"
        noIndex="true"
        priority="0.5">
        <content
            cq:lastRolledout="{Date}2022-09-13T15:37:21.057Z"
            cq:lastRolledoutBy="dylan_gibson@vfc.com"
            jcr:mixinTypes="[cq:LiveRelationship]"
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="foundation/components/parsys">
            <grid_row
                cq:lastRolledout="{Date}2022-09-13T15:37:21.069Z"
                cq:lastRolledoutBy="dylan_gibson@vfc.com"
                jcr:created="{Date}2021-03-10T00:54:33.861Z"
                jcr:createdBy="abbey_charles@vfc.com"
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2022-09-13T15:37:21.064Z"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="abbey_charles@vfc.com"
                jcr:mixinTypes="[cq:LiveRelationship]"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="vfcorp/components/global/content/grid_row">
                <row-content
                    cq:lastRolledout="{Date}2022-09-13T15:37:21.077Z"
                    cq:lastRolledoutBy="dylan_gibson@vfc.com"
                    jcr:mixinTypes="[cq:LiveRelationship]"
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="vfcorp/components/global/content/grid_row/parsys">
                    <grid_column_copy_cop
                        cq:lastRolledout="{Date}2022-09-13T15:37:21.092Z"
                        cq:lastRolledoutBy="dylan_gibson@vfc.com"
                        jcr:created="{Date}2020-09-18T20:27:24.616Z"
                        jcr:createdBy="abbey_charles@vfc.com"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2022-09-13T15:37:21.084Z"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="abbey_charles@vfc.com"
                        jcr:mixinTypes="[cq:LiveRelationship]"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="vfcorp/components/global/content/grid_column"
                        largeScreensCenterColumn="true"
                        largeScreensColumnCount="9"
                        mediumScreensCenterColumn="true"
                        smallScreensCenterColumn="true"
                        smallScreensColumnCount="11">
                        <column-content
                            cq:lastRolledout="{Date}2022-09-13T15:37:21.103Z"
                            cq:lastRolledoutBy="dylan_gibson@vfc.com"
                            jcr:mixinTypes="[cq:LiveRelationship]"
                            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                            sling:resourceType="vfcorp/components/global/content/grid_column/parsys">
                            <text
                                cq:lastRolledout="{Date}2022-09-13T15:37:21.124Z"
                                cq:lastRolledoutBy="dylan_gibson@vfc.com"
                                jcr:created="{Date}2020-09-18T20:28:22.736Z"
                                jcr:createdBy="abbey_charles@vfc.com"
                                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2022-09-13T15:37:21.113Z"
                                jcr:lastModifiedBy="abbey_charles@vfc.com"
                                jcr:mixinTypes="[cq:LiveRelationship]"
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                sling:resourceType="vfcorp/components/global/content/text"
                                marginBottom="bottom-margin-default"
                                marginTop="top-margin-default"
                                paddingBottom="bottom-pad-default"
                                paddingTop="top-pad-default"
                                text="&lt;h1 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/h1>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;h1 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/h1>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;h1 style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>THE ALTRA 15-15-15 CHALLENGE PROMOTION&lt;/h1>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>OFFICIAL RULES&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>NO PURCHASE NECESSARY.&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>VOID WHERE PROHIBITED BY LAW.&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>1. Eligibility&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>The Altra 15-15-15 Challenge Promotion (“Promotion”) is open only to legal residents of the United States and the District of Columbia who are at least eighteen (18) years old (or the age of majority in his/her/their jurisdiction of residence, whichever is older). Eligibility is further subject to having the Strava&amp;nbsp;GPS&amp;nbsp;Cycling and Running&amp;nbsp;App (via free or subscription service; type of service will not affect one’s ability to participate in the Promotion or his/her/their odds of winning) (“Strava App”).&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>The following persons are NOT eligible:&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>(a)&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Employees, officers and directors of Altra Running, a division of VF Outdoor, LLC (“Sponsor”), Strava, Inc. and their respective parent companies, divisions, subsidiaries and affiliated companies;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>(b)&amp;nbsp; the immediate families (defined as parent, child, sibling, spouse), regardless of where they live, of such employees/officers/directors; and&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>(c)&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; the members of the same household, whether related or not, of such employees/officers/directors.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Participation constitutes entrant’s full and unconditional agreement to these Official Rules and Sponsor’s decisions, which are final and binding in all matters related to the Promotion. Winning a prize is contingent upon fulfilling all requirements set forth herein.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>2. Sponsor&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Sponsor: Altra Running, a division of VF Outdoor, LLC, 1551 Wewatta St., Denver, CO 80202.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>3. Entry&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>There are two ways to enter this Promotion.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>A.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Entry via Strava App&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Beginning March 8, 2021 at or after 12:01 a.m. Eastern Time (ET), go to the Challenge Gallery in the Explore tab or in the Feed area of the Strava App and select “Altra Running 15-15-15 Challenge.” The Altra 15-15-15 Challenge (also referred to as “15-15-15 Challenge”) involves running 15 miles between March 15 and March 30, 2021. If a person completes the 15-15-15 Challenge, as recorded by the Strava App, he/she/they will receive a “completion badge” as well as a coupon code good for 15% off a qualifying purchase at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.altrarunning.com&quot;>www.altrarunning.com&lt;/a> (minimum required purchase, expiration date and other terms apply to use of coupon code).&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>BEFORE ENGAGING IN THE 15-15-15 CHALLENGE, IT IS STRONGLY RECOMMENDED THAT YOU CONSULT WITH A PHYSICIAN OR HEALTH CARE PROFESSIONAL TO CONFIRM THAT YOU ARE IN SUITABLE PHYSICAL CONDITION TO DO SO. IN ELECTING TO ENGAGE IN THE 15-15-15 CHALLENGE, YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT RUNNING CARRIES AN INHERENT RISK OF INJURY OR EVEN DEATH (INCLUDING SLIPS, FALLS, INJURY DUE TO THE EFFECTS OF WEATHER AND/OR ROAD CONDITIONS) AND, TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, YOU RELEASE SPONSOR AND STRAVA, INC. FROM LIABILITY FOR SAME UNDER ANY LEGAL THEORY. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>&amp;nbsp;IF YOU HAVE ANY DOUBTS AS TO YOUR ABILITY TO PARTICIPATE IN THE 15-15-15 CHALLENGE OR DO NOT ACCEPT THE RISK OF INJURY/DEATH IN CONJUNCTION THEREWITH, YOU ARE ADVISED NOT TO TAKE PART IN THE 15-15-15 CHALLENGE AND TO ENTER THE PROMOTION VIA THE MAIL-IN ENTRY METHOD SET FORTH BELOW.&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>By clicking on the REDEEM button in the “completion badge,” you will be re-directed to a website with an entry form. To enter the Sweepstakes, complete the entry form with all required information, including your name, the email address associated with your Strava account., your daytime telephone number and your state of residence. Entries must be received no later than 11:59 p.m. ET on April 1, 2021.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Strava, Inc. will only provide “completion badge” and Sponsor will only provide the 15% off coupon code if the Strava App determines that the user has run 15 miles between March 15 and March 30, 2021. Strava, Inc.’s determination of user’s completion of the 15-15-15 Challenge is final and binding in all respects, with Sponsor relying on the accuracy of same as to implementation of the Promotion. Sponsor disclaims any and all liability under any legal theory for the operation of Strava App and/or Strava, Inc.’s determination that a given user has (or has not) completed the 15-15-15&lt;sup> &lt;/sup>Challenge. Any attempt by an individual to undermine the operation of the Strava App, including but not limited to any misrepresentation or deception of any kind as to whether he/she/they actually completed the 15-15-15 Challenge will result in disqualification from the Promotion and may affect such individual’s continued use of the Strava App (via free or subscription service).&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>&lt;i>&lt;u>RECEIPT AND/OR REDEMPTION OF A “COMPLETION BADGE” OR A 15% OFF COUPON CODE FOR COMPLETING THE 15-15-15 CHALLENGE WILL NOT RESULT IN ENTRY IN THE RANDOM DRAWING.&lt;/u>&lt;/i>&lt;/b>&lt;i>.&lt;/i>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;i>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/i>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Accessing the Strava App and/or entering the Promotion on-line via mobile device may result in the imposition of wireless Internet access fees and/or other charges as per the wireless carrier’s billing policy. You are advised to review such billing policy BEFORE using the Strava App and/or entering the Promotion. Wireless Internet access is not available in all areas or on all mobile devices.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>B.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Entry via Mail&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>To enter&lt;b>&lt;u> without&lt;/u>&lt;/b> completing the 15-15-15 Challenge, print on a 3”x5” card your name, email address associated with your Strava account , daytime telephone number and state of residence and mail in a business size (#10) envelope to: The Altra 15-15-15 Challenge, 1515 Wewatta St. Denver, CO 80202 ATTENTION: 15-15-15 Challenge. Entries must be postmarked by April 2, 2021 and received by April 13, 2021. No copies or mechanical reproductions of mail-in entries will be accepted. Mail-in entries become Sponsor’s property and will not be returned. &lt;u>Those entering by mail will not receive the 15% off coupon code.&lt;/u>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>5. Additional Restrictions on Entry.&lt;b>&lt;u>&lt;/u>&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>&lt;u>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/u>&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>&lt;u>Limit of one (1) entry per person regardless of entry method utilized&lt;/u>&lt;/b>. Use of any device or artifice to violate the entry limit may result in disqualification from Promotion and may affect individual’s continued use of the Strava App (via free or subscription service).&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Proof of transmission of entry form does not constitute receipt of same or proof of entry.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Receipt of on-line entries will be acknowledged (including via issuance of 15% off coupon code); however, such acknowledgement is not binding upon Sponsor in any respect. Receipt of mail-in entries will NOT be acknowledged.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>In case of dispute as to ownership of entry, the entrant will be deemed to be the authorized account holder of the email address associated with the Strava account as per Strava, Inc.’s business records. The authorized account holder is the natural person who is assigned to the email address by an internet access provider, online service, or other organization that is responsible for assigning email addresses.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;6. Random Drawing, Winner Notification &amp;amp; Verification&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>On or about April 15, 2021, Sponsor will select winners in a random drawing from among all eligible entries received.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Each potential prize winner will be contacted using the email address and/or telephone number included on the entry (method[s] of winner notification to be determined by Sponsor in its sole discretion) and will be required to complete, sign and return a Declaration of Eligibility, a Liability Release and a Publicity Release (where legal) (“Declaration/Release”) within five (5) business days.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Prize will be forfeited without compensation of any kind and an alternate potential winner may be selected if any of the following occurs:&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>(a)&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Potential winner does not timely complete, sign and return the Declaration/Release;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>(b)&amp;nbsp; Potential winner cannot be contacted for any reason despite Sponsor’s commercially reasonable efforts to do so (by way of example only, potential winner’s email service provider categorizes winner notification email as “Junk” or SPAM, if applicable);&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>(c)&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; if Sponsor determines that the potential winner is ineligible or potential winner has otherwise in violated these Official Rules.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>8. Prizes and Approximate Retail Value&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Prizes (15) – One pair of Altra Running shoes to be awarded in the form a free product code redeemable at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.altrarunning.com&quot;>www.altrarunning.com&lt;/a>, with a value of up to $180.00. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>TOTAL APPROXIMATE RETAIL VALUE OF ALL PRIZES: UP TO $2700.00.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Odds of winning a prize depend on the number of eligible entries received for the applicable random drawing.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Free product code is valid only for 6 months from date of issuance; free product code may be used in multiple transactions prior to the expiration of the 6 month period, with any value remaining on free product code at such time being forfeited. Other terms apply to use of free product code. Any unspecified expenses relative to prize acceptance and use, including but not limited to transactions using free product code which exceed $180, are winner’s sole responsibility. All standard terms of sales on &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.altrarunning.com&quot;>www.altrarunning.com&lt;/a> govern redemption of free product code.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Limit of one (1) prize per family, household or address. Prize must be accepted as awarded; if declined for any reason, no compensation will be provided. THE ONLY WARRANTY ON PRIZE IS THE EXPRESS WARRANTY PROVIDED BY SPONSOR ON ITS PRODUCTS WHICH IS LIMITED TO ITS TERMS; TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, NO OTHER WARRANTY, REPRESENTATION OR GUARANTEE OF ANY KIND IS PROVIDED WITH PRIZE.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Winner is solely responsible for all federal, state and local taxes on prize. Prizes is nontransferable and may not be substituted or redeemed for cash. Sponsor reserves the right to substitute prize for one of equal or greater value due to prize unavailability for any reason.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>9. Discount code&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Coupon code redeemable at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.altrarunning.com&quot;>www.altrarunning.com&lt;/a> for 15% off the purchase of regularly priced item(s) with a minimum price of $60.00. To redeem, enter coupon code at checkout and click “Apply A Promo Code.”&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>By accepting coupon code, you represent and warrant that you completed the Altra 15-15-15 Challenge, running 15 miles between March 15 &amp;amp; 30, 2021.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Code expires (6) months after issuance and is valid for one-time use only. 15% price reduction is pre-tax and excludes expedited shipping charges.&amp;nbsp; Coupon code cannot be combined with other coupons, offers or discounts.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Coupon code is good only for original recipient of same (i.e., consumer who completed the Altra 15-15-15 Challenge.) We reserve the right to verify identity of consumer before honoring coupon code; this and all decisions of Altra are final and binding.&amp;nbsp;All purchases are subject to terms and conditions of &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.altrarunning.com&quot;>www.altrarunning.com&lt;/a>. We are not responsible if the coupon code is lost, stolen, destroyed or used without your permission&amp;nbsp;or for technological failure/error/malfunction of any kind.&amp;nbsp;Remaining balance&amp;nbsp;of merchandise purchase&amp;nbsp;must be paid using another form of payment. Coupon code cannot be redeemed for cash or applied as payment to any account.&amp;nbsp;Coupon code is not transferable and not to be republished.&amp;nbsp;No price adjustment allowed on previous purchases, product returns/exchanges&amp;nbsp;or purchases made without use of the coupon code.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Void where prohibited, taxed or restricted.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>10. Entry Conditions and Release&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>By entering, each entrant releases and agrees to hold harmless Sponsor and Strava, Inc.; their respective parent companies, divisions, subsidiaries and affiliated companies; all of their respective officers, directors, employees, agents, shareholders and representatives (collectively, the “Released Parties”) from and against any and all claims, expenses and liability, including but not limited to negligence, damages, or injury of any kind to persons and property, including but not limited to property damage, or death or personal injury arising out of or relating to a participant’s entry, participation in the Promotion, acceptance or use or misuse of prize (if applicable) and/or the broadcast, exploitation or use of entry; and (c) indemnify, defend and hold harmless the Released Parties from and against any and all claims, expenses, and liabilities (including reasonable attorneys’ fees) arising out of or relating to an entrant’s participation in the Promotion and/or entrant’s acceptance, use or misuse of any prize (if applicable).&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>11. Publicity&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Except where prohibited, acceptance of prize constitutes each winner’s consent to Sponsor’s and its agents’ use of each winner’s name, likeness, photograph, voice, opinions and/or hometown and state for promotional purposes in any media, worldwide, without further payment or consideration or review/approval of any kind.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>12. General Conditions&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Sponsor reserves the right to cancel, suspend and/or modify the Promotion, or any part of it, if any fraud, technical failures, pandemic/epidemic, materials shortage, civil commotion, riot, strike, natural disaster of any kind or any other factor beyond Sponsor’s control impairs the integrity or proper functioning of the Promotion, as determined by Sponsor in its sole discretion. In such event, to the extent feasible, Sponsor shall endeavor to conduct the Promotion and make the prizes available via random drawing from among all eligible Strava App entries received prior to the action taken by Sponsor as well as all eligible mail-in entries received or otherwise in a manner which Sponsor determines in its sole discretion is fair, appropriate and consistent with these Official Rules. Notification of such action by Sponsor will be posted on the Strava App. Sponsor reserves the right in its sole discretion to disqualify any individual Sponsor or Strava, Inc. find to be tampering with the procedure of participating in the Promotion, the operation of the Promotion or to be acting in violation of these Official Rules or in an unsportsmanlike or disruptive manner. Sponsor’s failure to enforce any term of these Official Rules in a given circumstance shall not constitute a waiver of that provision.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>13. Limitations of Liability&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>The Released Parties are not responsible for: (a) any incorrect or inaccurate information, whether caused by entrants, or programming associated with or used in the Promotion; (b) technical failures of any kind, including but not limited to malfunctions, interruptions, or disconnections in phone lines or network hardware or software; (c) unauthorized human intervention in any part of the Promotion, including but not limited to use of the Strava App; (d) technical or human error, which may occur in the administration of the Promotion, including but not limited to the recordation of user’s participation in the 15-15-15 Challenge or the processing of entries; or (e) any injury or damage to persons or property, which may be caused, directly or indirectly, in whole or in part, from entrant’s participation in the Promotion or receipt or use or misuse of any prize.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>The Released Parties are not responsible for late, lost, illegible/garbled, inaccessible, incomplete, damaged, misdirected, corrupted, jumbled on-line or mail-in entries or improperly recorded or unrecorded data as to completion of 15-15-15 Challenge, regardless of cause, all of which are void. The Released Parties are also not responsible for postage due mail.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>If for any reason an entrant’s entry is confirmed to have been erroneously deleted, lost or otherwise destroyed or corrupted, entrant’s sole remedy is another entry in the Promotion to the extent feasible; and, if not feasible, Released Parties shall not have any liability of any kind. No more than the stated number of prizes will be awarded.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>14. Disputes; Choice of Law&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>To the fullest extent permitted by law, entrant agrees that:&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>(A)&amp;nbsp; &lt;/b>any and all disputes regarding the Promotion or these Official Rules shall be governed by the internal, substantive law of Colorado (i.e., without regard to choice of law/conflict of law rules of Colorado or of any other jurisdiction);&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>(B)&amp;nbsp; &lt;/b>entrant is subject to the personal and exclusive jurisdiction of the United States District Court for the District of Colorado or Colorado State court situate in Denver County;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>(C)&amp;nbsp; &lt;/b>entrant waives any right of change of venue, inconvenient forum or the like;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>(D)&amp;nbsp; &lt;/b>any action will be brought by entrant individually (NOT as part of a class action);&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>(E)&amp;nbsp; &lt;/b>entrant’s recovery in any such action is limited to actual costs involved in participating in the Promotion (if any), with all rights to attorneys’ fees and any and all damages (including special, compensatory, punitive, consequential damages) being expressly waived.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>If the preceding or any other provision of these Official Rules is determined by a court of competent jurisdiction to be invalid, illegal or unenforceable, it shall be replaced by a substitute provision that most closely approximates the original intent of Sponsor and is valid, legal and enforceable. The invalidity/illegality/unenforceability of a given provision shall not affect the remainder of these Official Rules.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>14. Entrant’s Personal Information&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Information collected from participants is subject to the Sponsor’s Privacy Policy, which is available at: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.altrarunning.com/privacy-policy.html&quot;>www.altrarunning.com/privacy-policy.html&lt;/a> as well as Strava, Inc.’s Privacy Policy, which is available at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.strava.com/legal/privacy&quot;>https://www.strava.com/legal/privacy&lt;/a>. Be sure to read each Privacy Policy carefully before participating in the Promotion as they contain important information as how Sponsor and Strava, Inc. respectively each collect, use and share your personal information.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>15. Winners’ List&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>For the names of Winners, send a self-addressed stamped envelope to 1515 Wewatta St. Denver, CO 80202 ATTN 15-15-15 Challenge, for receipt by April 30, 2021.&amp;nbsp; Winners’ list will be available after May 15, 2021.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;"
                                textIsRich="true"/>
                        </column-content>
                    </grid_column_copy_cop>
                </row-content>
            </grid_row>
        </content>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
